out that have bankrupted the economy consistently again and again and again. In fact, there's
a pattern. Whenever we spend more than 3% of the overall GDP of the economy on an infrastructure
build out, it bankrupts the economy briefly for 10 years. So this happened when we did
railway tracks. In fact, it happened twice in the UK and twice in the USA. Then we bankrupt
ourselves putting the electrification grid in place. We bankrupted ourselves putting highways
in place. Now, there's something that makes this worse than ever before. And that is that
when we built train tracks, they lasted for 100 years. When we built roads, they lasted
50 plus years. The telecommunications, fiber optics, 30 years. All of these investments
were multi-decade investments that we could get benefit from and leverage for decades.
Data centers last three to four years before they need to be replaced. So we are building
something that has a three to four year lifecycle that costs hundreds of billions and it has
to be replaced every few years. And there is no financial model attached to this that
justifies it at all. So one thing that I'm predicting is that in 2029, 100 years after
the Great Depression, we will see a massive financial meltdown based off the back of these
data centers that have been developed at the moment. The technology itself is remarkable,
but the financial model just makes no sense whatsoever at the moment.